# **Zac Rice**

# California ● zacrice.dev ● zacrice2222@gmail.com ● (209)-269-0588

Developer based in California with 3 years of coding education. I have a passion for game development and expanding my knowledge base. Driven by the desire to collaborate on a project that achieves great success.

# **Work Experience**

January 2024 - April 2024

### CodeStack Internship - Web Developer

- Assisted with maintaining, debugging, and modifying existing code on large-scale applications.
- Added new features and updates to San Joaquin County Office of Education (SJCOE) applications, Captain, and IHub.
- Added new features to websites working full-stack using Angular, React, NextJs, C#, JavaScript, Typescript, and SQL.

March 2022 - December 2023

#### **Burlington** - Receiving

- Assisted in efficient unpacking and tagging of merchandise for placement on the sales floor, ensuring accuracy in pricing and labeling.
- Provided assistance to customers by engaging and assisting to identify their needs and answer questions. Offer recommendations and effectively guide customers to ensure satisfaction.

April 2019 - June 2020

#### The Habit - Cashier

- Responsible for accurately taking and fulfilling orders, managing money transactions, and working as a team to ensure customer satisfaction.
- Effective multitasking abilities by managing transactions, food preparations, and keeping things clean and organized.

### **Education**

September 2022 - January 2024

## CodeStack Academy - Stockton CA

• Immersive and accelerated 18-month program dedicated to project-based learning that requires strong commitment, communication, collaboration, creativity, time management and problem-solving skills. Learned the newest coding technology and built apps and websites from scratch

#### **Coding Languages:**

- C#

- JavaScript

- HTML

- CSS

- TypeScript

- Python

#### Technology:

Unity - React

- .NET - React-Native

- Node.Js - Angular

- GIT - Next.JS

GitHub - SQL

- Azure - Figma